eastmeeteast.com 2019-12-05

# Privacy Policy - EastMeetEast

Effective as of 6/12/14

Last Updated 4/17/19

EastMeetEast, Inc., (" **EastMeetEast** ", " **we** ", " **us** " or " **our** ") is committed to protecting the privacy of our users online. Accordingly we have developed this Privacy Policy (" **Policy** ") to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of data we receive from users of www.EastMeetEast.com (the " **Site** "). Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Site, services, features and content, to administer your use of the Site (together, the " **Service** ") and to enable users to enjoy and easily navigate the Site.

This Policy sets forth the policies and procedures of data and information, including but not limited to personally identifiable information, received from users of the Service. This policy is applicable to all visitors of the Site, and all other users, registered or otherwise, of the Service (collectively, " **visitors** ", " **users** " or " **you** "). By using the Service, you consent to your information being collected, disclosed and otherwise used as described in this Policy, which is incorporated by reference into the EastMeetEast Terms of Service (" **TOS** "). Unless otherwise defined in this Policy, terms used in this Policy have the same meanings as in our TOS. If you do not agree to the terms and conditions of this Policy, and the terms and conditions in our TOS, you are not authorized to use the Service.

As used in this policy, the terms "using" and "processing" information include using cookies on a computer, subjecting the information to statistical or other analysis and using or handling information in any way, including, but not limited to collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing and transferring information within our organization or among our affiliates within the United States or internationally.

The Service may contain links to other web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other web sites. These other web sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. When linking to another web site, you should read the privacy policy stated on that web site. This Policy only governs information collected on the Service.

Capitalized terms used herein but not otherwise defined herein have the meanings given to them in the TOS.

When you create a profile on EastMeetEast, your personal information may be visible to other applications we own, such as Ricestream.

## Changes to the Privacy Policy

We may amend, update or change this Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Policy, we will post the revised Policy here. If we make material changes to the Policy, we will notify you by an e-mail sent to the address specified in the account you create through the Site (your " **EastMeetEast Account** ") or by means of a notice on the Site once the change has become effective. You are encouraged to review the Policy from time to time in the event changes have been made. Your continued use of the Service indicates your assent to the Policy as posted and you agree that we may change it at any time, effective immediately.

## Information We Collect

We may collect information that can identify you personally, including but not limited to your name, email address, date of birth, zip code, and password (collectively, " **Personal Information** ") and other information that does not identify you. When you provide Personal Information through the Site, the information may be sent to servers located in the United States and other countries around the world.

  * Information you provide. We may collect and store any Personal Information you enter on the Site or provide to us in some other manner. This includes identifying information, such as your name, address, email address, and telephone number, and, if you transact business with us, financial information such as your payment method (valid credit card number, type, expiration date or other financial information). We also request information about your interests and activities, your gender and age, and other demographic information such as your hometown or your username.

  * Information about others. We may collect and store personal information about other people that you provide to us, such as their name, address and email address. If you use the Site to send others (friends, relatives, colleagues, etc.) a product as a gift, we may store your personal information, and the personal information of each such recipient in order to process those requests or facilitate future activities.

When you log in to an EastMeetEast Account and interact with our Service, we may automatically collect and store information that has the potential to be personally identifiable, such as your Internet Protocol (IP address). We only use and disclose user IP addresses under the same circumstances that we use and disclose Personal Information under this Policy.

You can also register to join the Site via an online account you may have with a third party service provider (a " **Third Party Account** "). For example, you may register to join the Site, and interact with the service, through a Third Party Account with a Social Networking Service (" **SNS** "). As part of the functionality of the Service, you may link your EastMeetEast Account with Third Party Accounts by either: (i) providing your Third Party Account login information to EastMeetEast through the Site; or (ii) allowing EastMeetEast to access your Third Party Account, as is permitted under the applicable terms and conditions that govern your use of each Third Party Account. You represent that you are entitled to disclose your Third Party Account login information to EastMeetEast and/or grant EastMeetEast access to your Third Party Account (including, but not limited to, for the use and for the purposes described herein), without breach by you of any of the terms and conditions that govern your use of the applicable Third Party Account and without obligating EastMeetEast to pay any fees or making EastMeetEast subject to any usage limitations imposed by the applicable SNS. If you decide to register by logging into a Third Party Account via our Site, we will obtain the Personal Information you have provided to the applicable SNS (such as your name, email address, profile picture, names of SNS friends, names of SNS groups to which you belong, other information you make publicly available via the applicable SNS and/or other information you authorize EastMeetEast to access by authorizing the SNS to provide such information) from your Third Party Accounts and use that information to create your EastMeetEast Account and EastMeetEast Account profile page, and you will become a Member. Depending on the Third Party Accounts you choose, and depending on the privacy settings that you have set in such Third Party Accounts, you understand that by granting us access to the Third Party Accounts, we will make available and store (if applicable and as permitted by the SNS and authorized by you) the information in your Third Party Accounts so that it is available on and through your EastMeetEast Account on the Site. If there is information about your SNS friends or people with whom you are associated in your Third Party Account, the information we obtain about those SNS friends or people with whom you are associated may also depend on the privacy settings such people have with the applicable SNS.

## EastMeetEast Accounts

When you create a EastMeetEast Account, we will set up an EastMeetEast Account profile page for you (" **EastMeetEast Profile Page** "), which will be generated on the Site. Your EastMeetEast Profile Page will include your name. You can select the other items of Personal Information that you wish to be included in your EastMeetEast Profile Page, including, but not limited to, a profile picture, a list of the SNS groups to which you belong, a list of any of your SNS friends or connections who are also users of EastMeetEast (collectively, your "Profile Information"). We will display your Profile Information on your EastMeetEast Profile Page publicly via the Site, and, with your prior permission, on third party sites. We recommend that you guard your anonymity and sensitive information and we encourage users to think carefully about what information about themselves they disclose in their profile pages. You can review and revise your Profile Information at any time.

## Changing or Deleting Your Information

All Members may review, update, correct or deactivate the Personal Information in their Profile Information by editing the relevant part of their EastMeetEast Profile Page. Please note that, if you deactivate your EastMeetEast Account, any recommendations or feedback you have posted via the Site will remain publicly viewable via the Site.

## How We Use Information

We use information we collect through the Service in order to provide, maintain, protect, and improve our Service, as well as to protect EastMeetEast and our Members.

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with EastMeetEast newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please click "unsubscribe" in the footer of the email or visit the "[Settings](http://www.eastmeeteast.com/accounts/edit)" page associated with your account to opt out of receiving such messages in the future.. Please note that we may also use your Personal Information to contact you with information related to your use of the Service; you may not opt out of these notifications.

We may transfer Personal Information as an asset in connection with a proposed or actual merger or sale (including any transfers made as part of an insolvency or bankruptcy proceeding) involving all or part of our business or as part of a corporate reorganization, stock sale or other change in control. In such a circumstance the transferee would be bound by the terms of this Policy.

We may combine your Personal Information with non-personally identifiable information and aggregate it with information collected from other Members in order to provide you with a better experience, to improve the quality and value of the Service, and to analyze and understand how our Site and Service are used. We may also use the combined information without aggregating it to serve you specifically, for instance to deliver a product or service to you according to your preferences or restrictions.

We may share non-personally identifiable information publicly and with connected sites or services. We only use this data in aggregate for business and administrative purposes, for the purposes of performing statistical analyses on user behavior and characteristics, for increasing the Service's functionality and user-friendliness, for demographic profiling, and to better tailor our Site to our visitors' needs. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your Personal Information. We also use this information to verify that visitors to the Site meet the criteria required to process their requests.

## How We Collect Information

We collect information via:

  * **Log Files.** Any time you visit the Site, our servers automatically gather information from your browser (such as your IP addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks) to analyze trends, administer the Site, prevent fraud, track visitor movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information. For example, we may log your IP address for system administration purposes. IP addresses are logged to track a user's session. This gives us an idea of which parts of our Site users are visiting. We do not share the log files externally.

  * **Information About You.** When you register or subscribe to any of our services, we collect a wide variety of information about you that you agree will be used to build your "Profile" and that this information will be available on the Site. You also agree that we may also display your marital status and most recent log-in date and other profile/account information to your matches. You may choose to provide us with your photo(s) and by providing us such content, you agree that we may make them available to your matches and users of EastMeetEast's services. Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not disclose your Personal Information to your matches or other users of our services.

  * **Purchase Information.** To process purchases, we may require your name, address, phone number, email address and credit card information. Such information is used primarily to process your order or as otherwise described herein. Credit card transactions are processed through industry standard Secure Socket Layer and/or strong encryption by a third party, which only uses your information for that purpose.

  * **E-mails.** We require an e-mail address from you when you register for our service. We use your e-mail for both transactional (e.g., order confirmation, refund and renewal processing, notifying of matches) and promotional (e.g., newsletters, new product offerings, special discounts, event notifications, special third-party offers) purposes. E-mail messages we send you may contain code that enables our database to track your usage of the e-mails, including whether the e-mail was opened and what links (if any) were clicked. If you would rather not receive promotional e-mails from us, please see the section below labeled "Your choices about collection and use of your information". We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the EastMeetEast services, such as service announcements and administrative messages, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. We fully comply with the requirements of the U.S. CAN-SPAM Act.

  * **Mobile Device.** If you use a mobile device to access our Site, we may collect device information (such as your mobile device ID, model and manufacturer), operating system and version information, and IP address. We collect your geolocational information only upon your consent.

  * **Demographic Data.** Demographic data is also collected at our Site. We use this data to tailor your experience at our Site, showing you Content that we think you might be interested in, and displaying the Content according to your preferences. Some of this information may be shared with advertisers on a non-personally identifiable basis.

  * **Online Survey Data.** We may periodically conduct voluntary member surveys. We encourage our Members to participate in such surveys because they provide us with important information regarding the improvement of our services. You may also volunteer for certain surveys that we may offer to our users, and any additional rules regarding the conduct of such surveys will be disclosed to you prior to your participation. We do not link the survey responses to any Personal Information, and all responses are anonymous.

  * **Public Forums.** Our blog contains posts which are relevant to dating and relationships and is available to our users and visitors. Any information that is disclosed in the comments section of any post becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any Personal Information. To request removal of your Personal Information from our blog, contact us at privacy@eastmeeteast.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your Personal Information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so.

  * **Use for Research.** In addition to the uses outlined above, by using our Site, you agree to allow us to anonymously use the information from you and your experiences to continue our research into successful relationships. This research, conducted by psychologists and behavior research scientists, may be published in academic journals. However, all of your responses will be kept anonymous, and no Personal Information will be published. You can find out more about the standards we follow in conducting scientific research by clicking here.

## Cookies

Like many websites, we use cookies to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies for two purposes. First, we utilize persistent cookies to save your login information for future logins to the Site. Second, we utilize session cookies to enable certain features of the Site, to better understand how you interact with the Site and to monitor aggregate usage by Members and visitors and web traffic routing on the Site. We use this information to improve the Service and make it appealing to as many users as possible. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Site or all functionality of the Service.

## Web Beacons

Our Site may contain electronic images known as web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our Site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.

## We may use information that we collect about you to:

  * deliver the products and services that you have requested;
  * manage your account and provide you with customer support;
  * perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our products, services, or content, or products, services or content offered by others;
  * communicate with you by email, and/or telephone about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us or other third parties;
  * develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on our Site and other sites;
  * verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with contests and sweepstakes;
  * enforce or exercise any rights in our terms and conditions;
  * manage our business;
  * provide EastMeetEast advertisements to you when you visit other sites; and
  * perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection

Financial information. We may use financial information or payment method to process payment for any purchases made on the Site, enroll you in the discount, rebate, and other programs in which you elect to participate, to protect against or identify possible fraudulent transactions, and otherwise as needed to manage our business.

Job applicants. If your Personal Information is submitted through the Site when applying for a position with our company, the information will be used solely in connection with considering and acting upon your application. We may retain your Personal Information for a period of time, but only for the purpose of considering you for current or future available positions. This information, which may include your name and contact information, prior education and experience, and other information you provided to us, may be shared with third-party service providers retained by us to collect, maintain and analyze candidate submissions for job postings.

Please review "Your choices about collection and use of your information" below.

## With whom we share your information

**Personal Information.** We do not share your Personal Information with others except as indicated below or when we inform you and give you an opportunity to opt out of having your Personal Information shared. We may share Personal Information with:

  * **Service providers.** We may share your Personal Information, which may include your name and contact information (including email address) with third parties that perform certain services on our behalf. These services may include fulfilling orders, providing customer service and marketing assistance, performing business and sales analysis, member screenings, supporting the Site functionality, and supporting contests, sweepstakes, surveys and other features offered through the Site. We may also share your name, contact information and credit card information with our authorized service providers who process credit card payments. These service providers may have access to Personal Information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purposes.
  * **Business partners.** When you register or make purchases on the Site or click-through our advertisements offered on third party websites, we may share Personal Information with the businesses with which we partner to offer you the applicable products, services or any advertisements. When you elect to engage in a particular merchant's offer or program, you authorize us to provide your email address and other information to that merchant. To opt-out of cookies that may be set by third party data or advertising partners, please go to http://www.aboutads.info/choices/.
  * **Other Situations.** We also may disclose your information, including Personal Information:

    * In response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order, or a request for cooperation from a law enforcement or other government agency; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases, we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us.
    * When we believe disclosure is appropriate in connection with efforts to investigate, prevent, or take other action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; to protect and defend the rights, property or safety of our company, our users, our employees, or others; to comply with applicable law or cooperate with law enforcement; or to enforce the Site's Terms or other agreements or policies.
    * In connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of our business, a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.
  * **Aggregated and/or non-personal information.** We may share non-personal information we collect under any of the above circumstances. We may also share it with third parties to develop and deliver targeted advertising on the Site and on websites of third parties, and to analyze and report on advertising you see. We may combine non-personal information we collect with additional non-personal information collected from other sources. We also may share aggregated, non-personal information, or personal information in hashed, non-human readable form, with third parties, including advisors, advertisers and investors, for the purpose of conducting general business analysis or other business purposes.

## Third-Party Advertising

We may use third-party advertising agencies or other service providers to serve ads on the Site on behalf of EastMeetEast or third-party advertisers (e.g., retailers of goods or services). These companies may employ cookies and web beacons to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and web beacons is completely anonymous. Some of these third-party advertising agencies may be members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers you the option to opt out of ad targeting from its member agencies by following the procedures listed [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Third Parties, with whom we partner to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity, use Flash cookies to collect and store information. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies click [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118)

## Security

We have extensive security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information stored in our database. These measures include the use of Secure Socket Layer and/or strong encryption technology during credit card transactions and administrative access to Site's data, as well as other proprietary security measures which are applied to all repositories and transfers of user information. We will exercise reasonable care in providing secure transmission of information between your computer and our servers, but given that no information transmitted over the Internet can be guaranteed 100% secure, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us over the Internet and hence accept no liability for any unintentional disclosure.

## Links to or Access from Other Sites

You may be able to access your account or content of your account from third party sites, such as social networking sites, by way of various applications. The privacy policies and practices of such sites in connection with information you disclose on such sites may differ from the practices of EastMeetEast as set forth in this Privacy Policy, and you should review their policies and practices to ensure that the privacy of the information you submit on their sites does not conflict with and is consistent with how you wish your information to be treated. Such sites may also place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices or the content of any other websites that may provide access to, or be linked to or from, our Site, including that of any social networking sites and third party advertisers whose offerings require you to navigate away from our Site.

## Your choices about collection and use of your information

  * You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but that may result in you being unable to use certain features of the Site because such information may be required in order for you to register as a member; purchase products or services; participate in a contest, promotion, survey, or sweepstakes; ask a question; or initiate other transactions on the Site.
  * At any time you can choose to no longer receive commercial or promotional emails from us by visiting the "Settings" page associated with your account. When you register on the Site, you will consent to receive email messages from us about special offers. You may modify this consent later by visiting the "Settings" page associated with your account. You also will be given the opportunity, in any commercial email that we send to you, to opt out of receiving such messages in the future. It may take up to 10 days for us to process an opt-out request. We may send you other types of transactional and relationship email communications, such as service announcements, administrative notices, and surveys, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. Please note that changing information in your account, or otherwise opting out of receipt of promotional email communications will only affect future activities or communications from us. If we have already provided your information to a third party (such as a service provider) before you have changed your preferences or updated your information, you may have to change you preferences directly with that third party.
  * You may tell us not to share your Personal Information with third parties for direct marketing purposes by visiting the "Settings" page associated with your account after you have registered.
  * You can also control information collected by cookies. See "Cookies" below for information about declining or deleting cookies.

## How you can access your information

If you have an online account with us, you have the ability to review and update your Personal Information online by logging into settings and clicking on your account settings. More information about how to contact us is provided below. If you have an online account with us, you also may delete or disable your account at any time by visiting the "[Disable My Account](http://www.eastmeeteast.com/accounts/deactivate)" page. If you delete or disable your account, we may still retain certain information associated with your account for analytical purposes and recordkeeping integrity, as well as to prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, enforce our terms and conditions, take actions we deem necessary to protect the integrity of the Site or our users, or take other actions otherwise permitted by law. In addition, if certain information has already been provided to third parties as described in this Privacy Policy, retention of that information will be subject to those third parties' policies.

## HOW YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IS PROTECTED

Your EastMeetEast Account is password protected for your privacy and security. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your username and password and you are fully responsible for all activities that occur under your username and password. You need to prevent unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password, and limiting access to your computer, phone and browser such as signing off after you have finished accessing your EastMeetEast Account. We are committed to protecting the information we receive from you, and we follow reasonable technical and management practices to help protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of Personal Information, potentially personally identifiable information, and data stored on our system. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures we have implemented reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved.

We restrict access to Personal Information to EastMeetEast employees, contractors and agents or affiliated organizations who need to know this information in order to process it for us, and who are subject to confidentiality obligations. We review our information collection, storage and processing practices, including physical security measures, to guard against unauthorized access to systems.

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Site-related services (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, web analytics, fraud detection services relating to the activity of EastMeetEast Members and improvement of the Site's features) or to assist us in analyzing how our Site and Service are used. These third parties may have access to your Personal Information; if they do, this access is only so that they may perform these tasks on our behalf and they are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

## Miscellaneous

### International Transfer

YOUR INFORMATION MAY BE TRANSFERRED TO - AND MAINTAINED ON - COMPUTERS LOCATED OUTSIDE OF YOUR STATE, PROVINCE, COUNTRY OR OTHER GOVERNMENTAL JURISDICTION WHERE THE PRIVACY LAWS MAY NOT BE AS PROTECTIVE AS THOSE IN YOUR JURISDICTION. IF YOU ARE LOCATED OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES AND CHOOSE TO PROVIDE INFORMATION TO US, EASTMEETEAST TRANSFERS PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THE UNITED STATES AND PROCESSES IT THERE. YOUR CONSENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY FOLLOWED BY YOUR SUBMISSION OF SUCH INFORMATION REPRESENTS YOUR AGREEMENT TO THAT TRANSFER.

### Our Policy Toward Children

The Site is not directed to individuals under 18. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files.

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us at privacy@eastmeeteast.com

## Acceptance of this Privacy Policy

Your use of our Site including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service. **BY USING OUR SITE, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE PRACTICES SET OUT IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE APPLICABLE TERMS OF SERVICE.**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy page and any other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, or by other means, such as e-mail, at our discretion.

Your continued use of any portion of the Site following posting of the updated Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes.
